Daniel Robert Rasmussen

SUMMARY

As a ten year business professional, I have switched gears and begun my transition towards a software engineering career. To meet this objective, I completed a twelve week immersive course that included 70+ hours per week of coding/architecture, including five projects using agile development practices.

RELEVANT SKILLS

LANGUAGES

Javascript, Ruby, SQL

TOOLS

Angular.js, Node.js, Express, Rails, PostgreSQL

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly, Seattle, Washington

2016

Web Development Immersive

- Completed several projects using multiple stacks while coding 70+ hours per week
- Developed a web application that utilized Yelp's API to locate local burger joints using Node and Javascript
- Developed a web application using Ruby/Rails to connect fellow kayakers
- Finished group sprint that utilized multiple news APIs and Angular is to list articles based on search queries

Soundview Medical Supply, Seattle, Washington

2013 - 2016

Customer Service Representative

- Maintained monthly customer contact via phone and email
- Ensured quality of monthly Medicaid orders while continually monitoring customer satisfaction

Eddie Bauer, Inc., Seattle, Washington

2011 - 2013

Sales Associate/Special Projects

- Helped customers coordinate casual and climbing outfits, sold credit and rewards cards, and maintained store appearance as well as provided occasional stockroom assistance
- Sent daily CSAT comments to regional directors, compiled and sent out weekly website technical problems, and assisted with additional projects as assigned by Call Center Head

Infinity Client Acquisitions, Inc., Saint Paul, Minnesota

2010 - 2011

Field Representative

• Sold DirecTv subscriptions to customers in Best Buy and Sam's Club retailers

State Farm Insurance, Shoreview, Minnesota

2010

Business Development

• Worked with hot and cold leads obtained from supervisor to offer quotes for many different insurance policies

Medstrom Surgical, Inc., St. Paul, Minnesota

2009 - 2010

Sales Representative

- Sold adipose relocation devices to plastic surgeons
- Provided quality assurance in operating room

Data Analyst

• Compiled detailed daily, weekly, monthly, and annual CT, MRI, X-Ray, Ultrasound, Mammography, and Bone Densitometry reports for marketing assistants, directors, and CEO

EDUCATION

General Asssembly, Seattle, Washington (2016)

Web Development Immersive

• Completed a twelve week immersive course that included 70+ hours per week of coding/architecture, including five projects using agile development practices

University of St. Thomas, Saint Paul, Minnesota (2006)

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.)

Business Administration major with Psychology minor